NYSUT Representative Assembly (RA) Audio-Visual materials 6174/013 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- '87 RA - People Enter Tom's Speech Intros, 1 (Box 149)
- '87 RA - Golden Apple, Tom Hobart (start), 2 (Box 149)
- '87 RA - End Hobart Start Gephart, 3 (Box 149)
- '87 RA - End Gephart, 4 (Box 149)
- '87 RA - Cuomo (switched), 5 (Box 149)
- '87 RA - Marc Tucker, Gordon Ambach, 6 (Box 149)
- '87 RA -Awards Ceasar Chavez - Floor Motions, 7 (Box 149)
- '87 RA - Resolutions Herb Megison Negotiation's, 8 (Box 149)
- '87 RA - Amendments Vote COPE Awards Resolutions, 9 (Box 149)
- '87 RA - Vote/COPE Award - Jerome Leckowitz, Harold Newman (I), 10 (Box 149)
- '87 RA - Harold Newman (II) Resolutions, 1 (Box 150)
- '87 RA - Resolutions Ed Cleary, 2 (Box 150)
- '87 RA - Teacher of Year, Intro School, 3 (Box 150)
- '87 RA - Sobol Resolutions, 4 (Box 150)
- '87 RA - Resolutions Philip Schlecty, 5 (Box 150)
- '87 RA - Philip Schlechty II, Amendments, Toni Cortese, Amendments, 6 (Box 150)
- '87 RA - Debate Motions Closing, 7 (Box 150)
- '87 RA - Cutaways from stage Hobart, 8 (Box 150)
- Shanker's Speech @1987 RA, 9 (Box 150)
- 1988 RA - tape #1 - Thursday evening - Vito Deleonardo, 1 (Box 151)
- 1988 RA - tape #3 - Friday, 2 (Box 151)
- 1988 RA - Tape #4 - Friday, 3 (Box 151)
- 1988 RA - Tape #9 - Saturday, 4 (Box 151)
- RA '89 Shanker - 'B' roll, 1989; 5 (Box 151)
  Edited
- 1989 RA - Friday, 6 (Box 151)
- Albert Shanker - reel 2, 7 (Box 151)
  tape 2 of 2
- Albert Shanker, President American Federation of Teachers -, 8 (Box 151)
  tape 1 of 2
- Comm. Thomas Sobol - NYSUT RA - Apr. 15, 1989, 9 (Box 151)
  Dub Master
- Al Shanker at 1988 RA, 10 (Box 151)
  VHS tape
- Journalism Awards - RA '89, 1989; 11 (Box 151)
- Eastern Airlines Speakers RA 1989 - Pilot, Attendant, Merchant, 1 (Box 152)
- Comm. Thomas Sobol - NYSUT RA Apr. 15, 1989 - Niagara Falls, NY, 2 (Box 152)
- RA 1989 - Antonia Cortese - NYSUT - First V.P. Early Childhood, 3 (Box 152)
- Inside Albany NYSUT - Asks for $1.5 billion, 4 (Box 152)
  dub Master
- Thomas Y. Hobart - NYSUT TA - Apr. 15, 1989 - Niagara Falls, NY, 5 (Box 152)
- Secretary of Labor, Elizabeth Dole - Friday, April 14, 1989 RA, 6 (Box 152)
- 1989 RA Opener, 7 (Box 152)
  Master
- RA - 1989, 8 (Box 152)
- RA '89 -, 1989; 9 (Box 152)
- RA '89 - Open, 1989; 10 (Box 152)
- 1989 RA - Friday, 1 (Box 153)
- 1989 RA - Friday, 2 (Box 153)
- 1989 RA - Friday, 3 (Box 153)
- 1989 RA - Saturday, 4 (Box 153)
- 1989 RA - Saturday, 5 (Box 153)
- Solerno 'Resolutions' - Part 1 of Tony Cortese - 1989 RA - Saturday, 6 (Box 153)
- 1989 RA Saturday, 7 (Box 153)
- 1989 RA - Saturday, 8 (Box 153)
- Walter Dunn - Stillwater, 9 (Box 153)
- End Resolutions - Thank Yous, 10 (Box 153)
- 1989 RA - Saturday, 11 (Box 153)
- Program Rec #1 - 3/28/1990, 1 (Box 154)
- Program Rec #4 - 3/28/1990, 2 (Box 154)
- Program Rec. - 3/29/1990, 3 (Box 154)
- Program Rec. - 3/29/1990, 4 (Box 154)
- Program REc. #4 - 3/29/1990, 5 (Box 154)
- Program Rec. #5 - 3/24/1990, 6 (Box 154)
- Program Rec. #6 - 3/24/1990, 7 (Box 154)
- Program Rec. #7 -, 8 (Box 154)
- Preview Rec. 1 - 3/24/1990, 9 (Box 154)
- B-Roll Tape -- 3/24/1990, 10 (Box 154)
- Sobol Speech at 1990 NYSUT RA, 11 (Box 154)
- Rehearsal - 3/22/1990 -- Big Cheese & Program, 1 (Box 155)
- Governor Cuomo's Address to the 1990 NYSUT RA in New York City - 3/22/1990, 2 (Box 155)
- Program/Prev. "b" Roll - 3/22/1990, 3 (Box 155)
- Program/Prev. in "B" Roll - 3/22/1990, 4 (Box 155)
- Program - 3/22/1990 - Reel #1, 5 (Box 155)
- RA '91, 1991; 6 (Box 155)
- RA '91, 1991; 7 (Box 155)
- RA '91 - P5, 1991; 8 (Box 155)
- RA '91 - P6, 1991; 9 (Box 155)
- RA '91 - P7, 1991; 10 (Box 155)
- Stand Alone "300,000 Strong" - NYSUT TV ads (for use at the 1990 RA), 11 (Box 155)
- RA '91 - P8, 1991; 1 (Box 156)
- RA '91 - P9, 1991; 2 (Box 156)
- RA '91 - P10, 1991; 3 (Box 156)
- Dub Masters of RA '91 Floor Debates, 1991; 4 (Box 156)
- NYSUT AFT Logos - RA '91, 1991; 5 (Box 156)
- RA '91 - Roll over, 1991; 6 (Box 156)
- RA '91 - Cut Away 1, 1991; 7 (Box 156)
- RA '91 - Cut Away - 2, 1991; 8 (Box 156)
- RA '91 - Cut Away 3, 1991; 9 (Box 156)
- RA '91 - Cut Away 4, 1991; 10 (Box 156)
- RA '91 - Cut Away 5, 1991; 11 (Box 156)
- RA '91 - Cut away 6, 1991; 1 (Box 157)
- RA '91 - Group 1 - tape #1, 1991; 2 (Box 157)
- RA '91 - #1, 1991; 3 (Box 157)
- NYSUT 4 - General Session 2 - 3/20 /1992, 4 (Box 157)
- NYSUT 2 - General Session 1, 5 (Box 157)
- NYSUT 1 - General Session 1, 6 (Box 157)
- NYSUT 3 - General Session 2 - 3/20/1992, 7 (Box 157)
- NYSUT 2 - General Session 2 - 3/20/1992, 8 (Box 157)
- NYSUT 1 - General Session 2 - 3/20/1992, 9 (Box 157)
- NYSUT 3 - General Session 3 - 3/21/1992, 10 (Box 157)
- Clinton, 11 (Box 157)
- Sat AM - Clinton, 12 (Box 157)
- Tape 4 Saturday PM NYSUT, 1 (Box 158)
- Tape 1 Saturday AM - NYSUT, 2 (Box 158)
- Tape 2 Friday - AM - NYSUT, 3 (Box 158)
- New York State United Teachers - Opening Session - March 3, 1994, 4 (Box 158)
- Tape 2 Friday PM - NYSUT, 5 (Box 158)
- Tape 3 Friday PM - NYSUT, 6 (Box 158)
- Tape 1 Friday PM - NYSUT, 7 (Box 158)
- Tape 2 - Saturday PM - NYSUT, 8 (Box 158)
- Tape 1 - Friday AM - NYSUT, 9 (Box 158)
- Tape 4 - Saturday AM - NYSUT, 10 (Box 158)
- Tape 3 - Saturday PM - NYSUT, 11 (Box 158)
- Tape 1 - Saturday PM - NYSUT, 12 (Box 158)
- Tape 2 - Saturday AM - NYSUT, 13 (Box 158)
- Tape 3 - Saturday AM - NYSUT, 14 (Box 158)
- General Session - March 4, 1994 - tape #1, 15 (Box 158)
- General Session - March 4, 1994 - tape #2, 16 (Box 158)
- General Session - March 5, 1994 - tape #1, 17 (Box 158)
- General Session - March 5, 1994 - tape #3, 18 (Box 158)
- General Session - March 5, 1994 - tape #2, 19 (Box 158)
- Tape 1 - Fri. - 3/19/1992, 20 (Box 158)
- NYSUT 2 - General Session 3 - 3/21/1992, 21 (Box 158)
- NYSUT 1 - General Session 3 - 3/21/1992, 22 (Box 158)
- NYSUT - HQ Shoot - tape #1, 1 (Box 159)
- NYSUT #2 - 2/10/1995 - tape #2, 2 (Box 159)
- NYSUT #3 - 2/10/1995 - tape #1, 3 (Box 159)
- NYSUT Interviews tape #1, 4 (Box 159)
- NYSUT Interviews - tape #2, 5 (Box 159)
- NYSUT #6 - Bob Carillo, 6 (Box 159)
- NYSUT #7 - NYSUT Interviews - tape #4, 7 (Box 159)
- NYSUT #8 - Toni McCann Edit - NYSUT Interviews tape #5, 8 (Box 159)
- NYSUT #9 - Mary McWilliams - Toni Cortese, 9 (Box 159)
- NYSUT #10 - NYSUT HQ B-Roll 3/3/1995; NYSUT Interviews - 3/4/1995, 10 (Box 159)
- NYSUT #11 - NYSUT Interviews - 3/4/1995 - Desmond #2, 11 (Box 159)
- NYSUT Interviews - 3/4/1995 - Also B-Roll of Meeting - Desmond #3, 12 (Box 159)
- NYSUT #13 - NYSUT Interviews - 3/4/1995 - Desmond #4, 13 (Box 159)
- Narration - Candid Music at end - 1996, 14 (Box 159)
- NY Hilton - NYSUT Tape #1 - 2/29/1996, 15 (Box 159)
- NY Hilton NYSUT 1996 - 2/29/1996 - tape #1A, 16 (Box 159)
- NYSUT 1996 - NY Hilton - 2/29/1996 - tape #2, 17 (Box 159)
- NYSUT 1996 - 2/29/1996 - tape #3, 18 (Box 159)
- NYSUT 1996 - NY Hilton - 2/29/1996 - tape #4, 19 (Box 159)
- NYSUT - Fri. Morning - tape #1, 1 (Box 160)
- NYSUT - Fri. Morning - tape #2, 2 (Box 160)
- NYSUT - Friday Afternoon - tape #1, 3 (Box 160)
- NYSUT - Friday Afternoon - tape #2, 4 (Box 160)
- NYSUT - Friday Afternoon - tape #3, 5 (Box 160)
- NYSUT - General Session - #3 - tape #6 - 5/3/1997, 6 (Box 160)
- NYSUT General Session #1 - 5/1/1997 - tape #1, 7 (Box 160)
- General Session #1 - 5/1/1997, 8 (Box 160)
- NYSUT General Session #1 - 5/1/1997 - tape #2, 9 (Box 160)
- General Session #1 - 5/1/1997, 10 (Box 160)
- NYSUT General Session #3 - 5/2/1997 - tape #4, 11 (Box 160)
- General Session #3 - 5/2/1997 - tape #4, 12 (Box 160)
- General Session #4 - 5/3/1997 - Tape #6, 13 (Box 160)
- Capital Steps - 5/2/1997 - tape #5, 14 (Box 160)
- Capital Steps - NYSUT - tape #5, 15 (Box 160)
- General Session #5 - 5/3/1997 - tape #8, 16 (Box 160)
- NYSUT General Session #2 - 5/2/1997 - tape #3, 17 (Box 160)
- NYSUT '97 - Community Service Awards - Scrolls, 1997; 1 (Box 161)
- Vote COPE Scroll, 2 (Box 161)
- NYSUT - Benefits on Display - Word Scramble, Door Prize Drawing, 3 (Box 161)
- General Session #4 - 5/3/1997 - tape #7, 4 (Box 161)
- NYSUT General Session #3 - 5/3/1997 - tape #7, 5 (Box 161)
- NYSUT General Session #4 - 5/3/1997 - tape #9, 6 (Box 161)
- NYSUT General Session #4 - 5/3/1997 - tape #8, 7 (Box 161)
- NYSUT - 1996 Candids, 8 (Box 161)
- MUP - UFT New Teacher, 9 (Box 161)
- Clinton Gore, 10 (Box 161)
  edited tribute
- NYSUT - Deceased Delegates and Local Leaders since 1996 RA, 11 (Box 161)
- Scrolls, 12 (Box 161)
- Turning Points, 13 (Box 161)
- Clinton/Gore, 14 (Box 161)
  Edited tribute to Albert Shanker
- UFT New Teacher Video - November 1, 1996, 15 (Box 161)
- ATA 1996 Teacher Profile "Steven Sullivan", 16 (Box 161)
- ATA 1996 - Teacher Profile "Steven Sullivan" - 5/2/1997, 17 (Box 161)
- Partners in learning a Parent Teacher Conference - segments 1-6, 18 (Box 161)
- NYSUT Overview, 19 (Box 161)
- United Federation of Teacher's Story, 20 (Box 161)
- NYSUT 1996 RA Highlights, 21 (Box 161)
- 1996 NYSUT Candids - Raw + Finished, 22 (Box 161)
- Partners in Learning - Parent Teacher Conference - Introduction, 23 (Box 161)
- NYSUT - Niagara Falls, New York - Apr. 23, 1999 - Morning Session, 1 (Box 162)
- NYSUT - Niagara Falls - April 23, 1999 - Afternoon - tape 1, 2 (Box 162)
- NYSUT - April 23, 1999 - Tape 2 - Afternoon, 3 (Box 162)
- NYSUT - Niagara Falls - April 22, 1999, 4 (Box 162)
- NYSUT - April 24 - Afternoon, 5 (Box 162)
- NYSUT - April 24, 1999 - Mid morning Session, 6 (Box 162)
- NYSUT - April 24, 1999 Morning Session, 7 (Box 162)
- July 12, 1999 - Interviews - Local Presidents Conference, 8 (Box 162)
- Commitment to Community Service, 9 (Box 162)
- Local Presidents Conference - July 12, 1999 - Key Note Speaker, 10 (Box 162)
- Peter White - 1999 - NYS Teacher of the Year, 11 (Box 162)
- NYSUT 1999 RA Highlights, 12 (Box 162)
- 1999 RA SRP of the Year Address, 13 (Box 162)
- Diversity in Education - 4/1/1999, 14 (Box 162)
- 1999 RA Hillary Clinton Address, 15 (Box 162)
- Diversity in Education - 4/1/1999, 16 (Box 162)
- NYSUT - School-Related Personnel We Make a Difference, 17 (Box 162)
- Gracey Communications NYSUT - Candids 1999, 18 (Box 162)
- SRP - Tom Allen, 19 (Box 162)
- NYSUT - 4/24/1999, 20 (Box 162)
  cass #3
- NYSUT - 4/24/1999, 21 (Box 162)
  cass #4
- NYSUT 4/24/1999, 22 (Box 162)
  cass #5
- NYSUT 4/24/1999, 23 (Box 162)
  cass #2
- NYSUT 4/24/1999, 24 (Box 162)
  cass #1
- 1999 RA Highlights, 1 (Box 163)
- 1999 RA Highlights, 2 (Box 163)
- Diversity in Education Video Loop - 4/1/1999, 3 (Box 163)
- School Related Personnel - We Make a Difference - 4/6/1999, 4 (Box 163)
- School Related Personnel - We make A Difference - 4/6/1999, 5 (Box 163)
- Commitment to Community Service, 6 (Box 163)
- 1999 RA Hillary Clinton Address, 7 (Box 163)
- Commitment to Community Service, 8 (Box 163)
- 1999 RA - North Tonawanda High School Chorale, 9 (Box 163)
- Vote COPE - '99, 1999; 10 (Box 163)
- 1999 RA Proceedings - tape 1 - Thursday 4/22, 11 (Box 163)
- 1999 RA Proceedings - tape 2 - Friday 4/23, 12 (Box 163)
- 1999 RA Proceedings - tape 3 - Friday 4/23, 13 (Box 163)
- 1999 RA Proceedings - tape 6 - Saturday 4/24, 14 (Box 163)
- 1999 RA Proceedings - tape 5 - Saturday 4/24, 15 (Box 163)
- 1999 RA Proceedings - tape 4 - Friday 4/23, 16 (Box 163)
- 1999 NYS Teacher of the Year, 17 (Box 163)
- 1999 Teacher of the Year - 12/18/1998, 18 (Box 163)
- 1999 RA Proceedings - tape 7 - Saturday 4/24, 19 (Box 163)
- 1999 RA Hillary Clinton Address, 20 (Box 163)
- NYSUT - SRP of the Year - 1998, 21 (Box 163)
- NYSUT - Diversity in Education Video Loop - 4/1/1999, 22 (Box 163)
- NYSUT '96 - 3/1/1996 - tape #14 - NY Hilton, 1 (Box 164)
- NYSUT '96 - NY Hilton - 3/1/1996 - tape #12, 2 (Box 164)
- NYSUT 1996 - NY Hilton - 3/1/1996 - tape #13, 3 (Box 164)
- NYSUT '96 - tape #10 - 3/1/1996, 4 (Box 164)
- NYSUT '96 - NY Hilton - 3/1/1996 - tape #11, 5 (Box 164)
- NYSUT '96 - tape #8 - 3/1/1996 - NY Hilton, 6 (Box 164)
- NY Hilton - NYSUT '96 - tape #9 - 3/1/1996, 7 (Box 164)
- NYSUT #5 - 2/29/1996 - NY Hilton, 8 (Box 164)
- NYSUT '96 - 3/1/1996 - tape #6 - Reich, 9 (Box 164)
- NYSUT '96 - 3/1/1996 - tape #7 - Reich, 10 (Box 164)
- Reels 9-12, 11 (Box 164)
  VHS cassette
- 24, 12 (Box 164)
- Reels 13-19, 13 (Box 164)
- General Session #5 - 5/3/1997 - tape #9, 14 (Box 164)
- Tape 30 - RA 96, 1996; 15 (Box 164)
- General Session #2 - 5/2/1997 - tape #3, 16 (Box 164)
- Reel #4-#9, 17 (Box 164)
- International Affairs - "The Road to Democracy" - 7/30/1990, 18 (Box 164)
- 1995 AFL-CIO Convention - Harry Wu Video, 19 (Box 164)
- Reels 1-4 - includes reel 1A, 20 (Box 164)
- NYSUT - Session #3 - 4/8/2000 (Box 165)
- NYSUT - Session #3 - 4/8/2000 (Box 166)
- NYSUT - Session #3 - 4/8/2000 (Box 167)
- NYSUT - 4/8/2000 (Box 168)
- NYSUT - Session #3 -- 4/8/2000 (Box 169)
- NYSUT - Session #2 - 4/7/2000 (Box 170)
- NYSUT #2 - 4/7/2000 (Box 171)
- NYSUT - Session #2 - 4/7/2000 (Box 172)
- NYSUT - Session #2 - 4/7/2000 (Box 173)
- NYSUT - Opening Session #1 (Box 174)
- NYSUT - Opening Session #1 - 4/6/2000 (Box 175)
- NYSUT - Session #3 -- 4/8/2000 (Box 176)
- NYSUT - Session #3 - 4/8/2000 (Box 177)
- NYSUT - Session #4 - 4/8/2000 (Box 178)
- NYSUT - Session #4 - 4/8/2000 (Box 179)
- NYSUT - Session #4 - 4/8/2000 (Box 180)
- NYSUT - Session #4 -- 4/8/2000 (Box 181)
- NYSUT - Session #2 -- 4/7/2000 (Box 182)
- NYSUT - Session #2 -- 4/7/2000 (Box 183)
- NYSUT 2 - Gen. Session 1 (Box 184)
- NYSUT 1 - Gen. Session 2 (Box 185)
- NYSUT 2 Gen. Session 2 (Box 186)
- NYSUT 5 - Gen. Session (Box 187)
- NYSUT 1 - Gen. Session (Box 188)
- NYSUT 2 - Gen. Session 3 (Box 189)
- NYSUT 3 - Gen. Session 3 - 3/21/1992 (Box 190)
- NYSUT 4 - Gen. Session 3 - 3/21/1992 (Box 191)
- NYSUT 1 + 3 - Gen. Session 3 - 3/21/1992 (Box 192)
- NYSUT 2 + 4 - Gen. Session - 3/21/1992 (Box 193)